Guide to the United Federation of Teachers Hans Weissenstein Negatives PHOTOS 019 001
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series XI: Legislative and Government.
  - Functional Chapters Contract Signing Board of Education, May 13, 1970 (Box 12, Item 12585)
  - Local School Board Jerry Levine, May 18, 1970 (Box 12, Item 12592)
  - District Supt. Office District 28, Jun 15, 1970 (Box 14, Item 12682)
  - School Board press conference PS 6, Oct 29, 1970 (Box 15, Item 12853)
  - Queens Boro Presidents - Drug Program, Feb 19, 1971 (Box 17, Item 13086)
  - Abe Levine at City Hall budget hearing, Feb 23, 1971 (Box 18, Item 13090)
  - Dr. Schreiber Board of Education HS Committee, Mar 31, 1971 (Box 18, Item 13183)
  - Board of Education - Brooklyn, Apr 22, 1971 (Box 19, Item 13216)
  - Board of Education Abe Levine speaking, Apr 26, 1971 (Box 19, Item 13229)
  - Board of Education Abe Levine congratulating I[saiah?] Robinson, new pres[ident] of BOE, May 11, 1971 (Box 20, Item 13282)
  - Boro Pres. Queens, Oct 7, 1971 (Box 23, Item 13511)
  - Queens Boro Pres., Nov 15, 1971 (Box 24, Item 13625)
  - PS 23 Bronx New Supt., Nov 18, 1971 (Box 24, Item 13636)
  - Local School Board, Dec 15, 1971 (Box 25, Item 13739)
  - Senator Hobson - Manhattan Office, Dec 21, 1971 (Box 25, Item 13771)
  - Queens Boro Pres. Swearing in, Jan 8, 1972 (Box 25, Item 13783)
  - Local School Board #1 PS 34, Feb 16, 1972 (Box 27, Item 13850)
  - Queens Boro Pres., Feb 17, 1972 (Box 27, Item 13843)
  - Comm. [?] School Board District 6 Manhattan, Wadsworth, Feb 17, 1972 (Box 27, Item 13847)
  - City Hall Hearing Abe Levine, Feb 23, 1972 (Box 27, Item 13867)
  - City Hall Hearings, Feb 24, 1972 (Box 27, Item 13871)
  - Board of Education HS Comm., Mar 7, 1972 (Box 27, Item 13886)
  - Local School Board Candidates, Mar 22, 1973 (Box 29, Item 14271)
  - District 6 School Board [Whitestone Photos], May 5, 1974 (Box 30, Item 14631)
- Series XII: Meetings.
  - Teachers' Guild - Fannie Hurst [Speaking (to members?) at Guild meeting.], Feb 6, 1954 (Box 1, Item 1676)
  - Teachers' Guild group head presentation, Oct 2, 1956 (Box 1, Item 3171)
  - Teachers' Guild meeting Trade High School, Feb 22, 1957 (Box 1, Item 3486)
  - Teachers' Guild [meeting], May 24, 1957 (Box 1, Item 3625)
  - NY Teachers' Guild Pension Meeting, Dec 4, 1959 (Box 2, Item 5249)
  - St. Nicholas Arena - wide shot, Mar 25, 1960 (Box 2, Item 5529)
  - St. Nicholas Arena - Teachers with Placards, Mar 25, 1960 (Box 2, Item 5529)
  - Teachers St. Nicholas Arena, Mar 25, 1960 (Box 2, Item 5529)
  - Board [meeting], Jan 9, 1962 (Box 2, Item 7398)
  - Strike Captains' Meeting, Mar 23, 1962 (Box 3, Item 7545)
  - Strike Captains [Meeting], Mar 23, 1962 (Box 3, Item 7545)
  - After School Rec. meet[ing], Dec 14, 1963 (Box 3, Item 8036)
  - Meetings, Jan 25, 1964 (Box 3, Item 8101)
  - Union Meeting, Oct 13, 1965 (Box 4, Item 9322)
  - Mass Meeting Marc Ballroom Evening, Oct 21, 1965 (Box 4, Item 9342)
  - Mass Meeting Marc Ballroom Afternoon, Oct 21, 1965 (Box 4, Item 9341)
  - Meeting at the George Washington Hotel, Dec 13, 1965 (Box 4, Item 9469)
  - Board of Education Budget Meeting Dr. [Jules] Kolodny, Dec 21, 1965 (Box 4, Item 9493)
  - Meeting [David] Wittes, Feb 20, 1966 (Box 4, Item 9675)
  - PS 113 [meeting in school library], Dec 23, 1966 (Box 5, Item 10216)
  - Meeting Hotel Granada, Jan 24, 1967 (Box 5, Item 10258)
  - George Washington Hotel Librarians, May 14, 1967 (Box 5, Item 10497)
  - Meeting Afro-American, May 18, 1967 (Box 5, Item 10503)
  - [More?] Effect[ive] Schools, Jan 19, 1968 (Box 6, Item 11011)
  - Chapter Meeting Marc Ballroom, May 28, 1968 (Box 6, Item 11256)
  - Madison Square Garden [Appears to be a meeting of all UFT chapters/members. Different chapters and school/district representatives are noticeable, holding up signs of their delegations.], Nov 17, 1968 (Box 6, Item 11502)
  - Albany [meeting], Apr 22, 1969 (Box 30, Item 15594)
  - Marc Ballroom Election Meeting, May 22, 1969 (Box 8, Item 11905)
  - School Rep. Meeting & Headshots Gramercy Sq. Hotel [Unidentified Individuals], Jun 19, 1969 (Box 8, Item 11979)
  - Brandeis H. S. [meeting], Oct 20, 1969 (Box 9, Item 12124)
  - Para-Professionals [meeting and front façade of UFT building]], Oct 21, 1969 (Box 9, Item 12123)
  - Marc Ballroom [meeting], Nov 3, 1969 (Box 9, Item 12169)
  - Executive Board Meeting UFT H. Q., Dec 8, 1969 (Box 9, Item 12259)
  - HS Meeting at UFT, Dec 11, 1969 (Box 9, Item 12276)
  - President Meet. Staten Island, Dec 12, 1969 (Box 9, Item 12277)
  - Para-Professionals [meeting], Jan 9, 1970 (Box 10, Item 12319)
  - Secretaries Meeting, Jan 30, 1970 (Box 10, Item 12369)
  - School Secretaries Meeting George Washington Hotel, Feb 26, 1970 (Box 11, Item 12411)
  - 35mm [meeting], Mar 16, 1970 (Box 30, Item 15600)
  - Gramercy Hotel Students & Union [meeting], Apr 17, 1970 (Box 12, Item 12521)
  - Secretaries [meeting], Nov 19, 1970 (Box 16, Item 12906)
  - Bronx / H.S. [meeting and headshots of unidentified individuals], Dec 8, 1970 (Box 16, Item 12945)
  - Music Teachers Committee Meeting, Dec 11, 1970 (Box 16, Item 12960)
  - MES Meeting Executive Board Room, Dec 18, 1970 (Box 16, Item 12976)
  - PS 332 Brooklyn meeting Velma Hill, Jan 7, 1971 (Box 25, Item 13785)
  - John Dewey HS Brooklyn Committee Meeting, Feb 24, 1971 (Box 18, Item 13095)
  - PS 29 District 15 Meeting - Brooklyn, Mar 24, 1971 (Box 18, Item 13170)
  - IS 88 [meeting], Apr 2, 1971 (Box 18, Item 13188)
  - PS 206 Brooklyn Chapter Meeting, Apr 21, 1971 (Box 19, Item 13215)
  - Pension at PS 83 [?] Ed Fuoriy [?], May 1, 1971 (Box 20, Item 13283)
  - Mus[eum?] Membership, May 11, 1971 (Box 20, Item 13289)
  - UFT at PS 2 District 2 Para-Professional Meeting, Velma Hill, Frank Brown, May 27, 1971 (Box 21, Item 13344)
  - Abe Levine - first meeting, Oct 5, 1971 (Box 23, Item 13502)
  - Chapter Chairman Meeting Marc Ballroom, Oct 6, 1971 (Box 23, Item 13505)
  - District 22 CC Meeting Dan Sanders & Ivan Tiger, Feb 10, 1972 (Box 26, Item 13830)
  - PS 110 security meeting Bronx, Apr 24, 1972 (Box 28, Item 13954)
  - Bronx Boro office emergency meeting of Chapter, May 5, 1972 (Box 28, Item 13975)
- Series XIII: Officers and Official Business.
  - Teachers' Guild Group - Sheraton (officers), May 3, 1953 (Box 1, Item 1151)
  - NY Teachers Charter, Jun 15, 1960 (Box 2, Item 5734)
  - [United Federation of] College [Teachers] Charter, Apr 29, 1963 (Box 3, Item 7628)
  - Dr. Gross, Supt. Swearing in Dr. [ David] Wittes, May 9, 1963 (Box 3, Item 7666)
  - Del[egate] Assembly Strike vote Roosevelt Aud[itorium], Jun 8, 1963 (Box 3, Item 7742)
  - Swearing in Officers Marc Ballroom, Jun 10, 1964 (Box 4, Item 8431)
  - Executive Board, Apr 28, 1965 (Box 4, Item 8990)
  - Legisl. Comm. with Comptroller Boraccio, Jan 21, 1966 (Box 4, Item 9563)
  - Delegate Assembly, Sep 6, 1968 (Box 6, Item 11328)
  - Delegate Meeting, Washington Irving HS., Sep 10, 1968 (Box 6, Item 11343)
  - Delegate Meeting Marc Ballroom, Sep 12, 1968 (Box 6, Item 11347)
  - Delegate Assembly Washington Irving HS, Oct 8, 1968 (Box 6, Item 11396)
  - Delegate Assemblies & Roosevelt Ass. Washington Irving [high school?], Oct 13, 1968 (Box 6, Item 11411)
  - Delegate Assembly Manhattan Center, Oct 23, 1968 (Box 6, Item 11436)
  - District Reps., Mar 14, 1969 (Box 7, Item 11715)
  - Delegate Assembly Fashion H.S., Jun 24, 1969 (Box 8, Item 11982)
  - District Reps. Lecture - John Hill - Sandy Feldman - [David] Wittes, Sep 22, 1969 (Box 8, Item 12063)
  - Executive Board Meeting UFT H. Q., Dec 8, 1969 (Box 9, Item 12259)
  - President Meet. Staten Island, Dec 12, 1969 (Box 9, Item 12277)
  - District Chapter Chairmen Marc Ballroom, May 5, 1970 (Box 12, Item 12564)
  - Delegate Ass[embly], Jun 24, 1970 (Box 14, Item 12698)
  - District 2 Reps, Dec 17, 1970 (Box 16, Item 12977)
  - Delegate Assembly Park Sheraton, Feb 17, 1971 (Box 17, Item 13080)
  - Delegate Assembly, Mar 10, 1971 (Box 18, Item 13138)
  - Chapter Chairman H. S. [of] Fashion [Industries], May 6, 1971 (Box 20, Item 13269)
  - Exec. Board, May 10, 1971 (Box 20, Item 13284)
  - Chapter Chairman Meeting Marc Ballroom, Oct 6, 1971 (Box 23, Item 13505)
  - Chapter Chairmen's Meeting with Albert Shanker, John Hill, Oct 8, 1971 (Box 23, Item 13516)
  - Bronx Boro Office Congressman Scheuer, Oct 22, 1971 (Box 23, Item 13557)
  - PS 274 Brooklyn chapter chair retiring Alan Luben [?], Nov 19, 1971 (Box 24, Item 13653)
  - Chapter Chairman Meeting JHS 143, Nov 23, 1971 (Box 24, Item 13662)
  - Marc Ballroom Chapter Chairman Meeting Albert Shanker Speaking, Dec 15, 1971 (Box 25, Item 13734)
- Series XIV: Parents.
  - LSA PTA C [?] C [?] Party, Sep 26, 1968 (Box 6, Item 11376)
  - PTA Marc Ballroom, Oct 16, 1968 (Box 6, Item 11425)
  - Brooklyn PTA/Teachers JHS 142, Mar 1, 1969 (Box 7, Item 11690)
  - PS 40 Queens Parent Teacher Luncheon, Apr 26, 1969 (Box 7, Item 11816)
  - PS 39 Party by PA to teachers, May 29, 1969 (Box 8, Item 11922)
  - PS 219 Brooklyn Parents Workshop, Jan 26, 1970 (Box 10, Item 12359)
  - PS 60 Spanish Class for Parents, Apr 28, 1970 (Box 12, Item 12544)
  - Parent Boycott School PS 11 Bronx, Sep 14, 1970 (Box 14, Item 12746)
  - PS 335 Brooklyn Talent Show for Parents & Teachers, Dec 21, 1970 (Box 16, Item 12982)
  - 196 K Teacher - Mom Program Brooklyn [Collection includes corresponding print for negative # 13112-1.], Mar 3, 1971 (Box 18, Item 13112)
  - Parents Recognition Day - PS 155 Manhattan, Apr 27, 1971 (Box 19, Item 13241)
  - HS Art & Design Parents/Teachers Meeting, Oct 6, 1971 (Box 23, Item 13508)
  - JHS 65 or 46 Manhattan PTA, Ivan Tiger, John Hill, Oct 8, 1971 (Box 23, Item 13520)
  - PTA Mrs. Aronow School for the Deaf, Oct 26, 1971 (Box 23, Item 13565)
  - PS 190 Panel PTA, Dec 2, 1971 (Box 25, Item 13693)
  - PS 26 Queens PTA Tea, May 15, 1972 (Box 29, Item 14000)
- Series XV: Political.
  - Secretaries petitions Board of Education, Jun 18, 1962 (Box 2, Item 7059)
  - Senior Citizens [Forum] Departure [to Democratic National] Convention [in Atlantic City], Aug 26, 1964 (Box 4, Item 8481)
  - Picket Line Welfare Workers, Jan 12, 1965 (Box 4, Item 8747)
  - Welfare Workers Picket Line at City Hall, Jan 18, 1965 (Box 4, Item 8774)
  - Albany Railroad Caravan [lobbying for passage of Calandra-Steingut Bill for teacher pensions], Feb 13, 1967 (Box 5, Item 10292)
  - Departure to Albany, May 20, 1968 (Box 6, Item 11219)
  - Poor People['s March] Departure, Jun 19, 1968 (Box 6, Item 11287)
  - ATMC) [?] Albany [UFT members meeting with Assemblyman George A. Cincotta, Assemblyman Moses Weinstein and others], Mar 24, 1969 (Box 7, Item 11736)
  - Grape picket line [Support demonstration for United Farm Workers' grape boycott; one frame includes both UFW president Cesar Chavez apparently speaking with reporters and UFT president Albert Shanker speaking into microphone.], Oct 10, 1969 (Box 8, Item 12097)
  - Committees Para-Professionals [Roberta L. ] Fass/[Jacqueline F.] Lander GE grape [Teaching Unit on the "Struggle of the Farm Workers for Collective Bargaining".], Nov 24, 1969 (Box 9, Item 12233)
  - Grapes, Albert Shanker [seated with boxes of "Union Label Table Grapes" in support of United Farmworkers AFL-CIO], Jun 1, 1970 (Box 13, Item 12631)
  - Board of Education Albert Shanker & [Murray] Bergtraum leaving for Albany, May 11, 1971 (Box 20, Item 13280)
  - Central Labor Council Voter Registration, Jun 1, 1971 (Box 21, Item 13364)
  - Lincoln Square Democratic Club, Jun 29, 1971 (Box 22, Item 13441)
  - Jewish Labor Committee on Soviet Jewry, Nov 4, 1971 (Box 24, Item 13607)
  - Manhattan Political Action Committee, Nov 22, 1971 (Box 24, Item 13659)
  - PAC [five people at table], Dec 13, 1971 (Box 25, Item 13724)
  - [Political Action] Conference, Dec 13, 1971 (Box 25, Item 13725)
  - PAC Freeman [seated with others], Feb 18, 1972 (Box 27, Item 13845)
  - PAC DeFalco [seated with others], Feb 18, 1972 (Box 27, Item 13846)
  - Coop City Ass. [?] Board, Israel Bonds, Eugene Kaufman, Feb 23, 1972 (Box 27, Item 13870)
  - Soviet Jewry Solidarity Day, Apr 30, 1972 (Box 28, Item 13965)
  - [Professional Staff Congress] City University Bus to Albany [with "Save Open Admissions and Free Tuition" signs], May 9, 1973 (Box 30, Item 14334)
- Series XVI: UFT Programs.
  - Blood [Drive], Jan 27, 1964 (Box 3, Item 8102)
  - Labor Exhibit Staffer[s], May 15, 1964 (Box 3, Item 8321)
  - M.E.S. Picket Line City Hall, Jun 22, 1967 (Box 5, Item 10586)
  - [More?] Effect[ive] Schools, Jan 19, 1968 (Box 6, Item 11011)
  - MES at NCCJ, May 13, 1969 (Box 8, Item 11880)
  - MES Conf. PS 109, May 17, 1969 (Box 8, Item 11884)
  - QuEST [Quality Educational Standards in Teaching] Comm., Sep 30, 1969 (Box 8, Item 12082)
  - QuEST Lecture, Jan 5, 1970 (Box 16, Item 12990)
  - MES [?] conf. NCCJ [National Conference for Community and Justice], Mar 13, 1970 (Box 11, Item 12443)
  - MES Sessions Chas. Evans Hughes H.S., Apr 25, 1970 (Box 12, Item 12538)
  - James Monroe H.S. Narcotics Program Brotherhood Estate [?], May 19, 1970 (Box 12, Item 12595)
  - MES Head Horkuse [?] James Group, Jun 5, 1970 (Box 13, Item 12648)
  - MES courses PS 307 K, Jun 6, 1970 (Box 13, Item 12649)
  - MES Conf. Tarrytown, Oct 31, 1970 (Box 15, Item 12861)
  - QuEST Committee, Dec 8, 1970 (Box 16, Item 12946)
  - MES Meeting Executive Board Room, Dec 18, 1970 (Box 16, Item 12976)
  - QuEST Magnetic Tape, Jan 26, 1971 (Box 17, Item 13034)
  - QuEST Program PS 181, Jan 27, 1971 (Box 17, Item 13039)
  - JHS 17 Manhattan Drug Out, Feb 5, 1971 (Box 17, Item 13055)
  - QuEST - Dance, Feb 9, 1971 (Box 17, Item 13066)
  - QuEST Art, Mar 3, 1971 (Box 18, Item 13116)
  - QuEST [teachers learning how to use] Cuisenaire [Rods], Mar 8, 1971 (Box 18, Item 13126)
  - Roosevelt HS Velma Hill: World of Work Program 70 [?] Central Labor Council, Mar 22, 1971 (Box 18, Item 13158)
  - PS 9 Brooklyn Drug Program, Mar 30, 1971 (Box 18, Item 13173)
  - IS 80 Bronx Drug Program for JHS Students, Apr 19, 1971 (Box 19, Item 13280)
  - IS 80 Bronx Drug Program for JHS students, Apr 19, 1971 (Box 20, Item 13280)
  - PS 70 Bronx Drug Program, Apr 21, 1971 (Box 19, Item 13214)
  - NCCJ MES Exhibit, Jun 11, 1971 (Box 22, Item 13394)
  - QuEST Course Gramercy Park Hotel, Ray Frank, Nov 11, 1971 (Box 24, Item 13619)
  - QuEST Courses 109 - 110 - 111 - 124, Nov 30, 1971 (Box 25, Item 13691)
  - QuEST Courses 114 - 112 - 125 - 113, Dec 2, 1971 (Box 25, Item 13692)
  - Sickle Cell Anemia Program PS 332 Brooklyn, Murry Sussman, Dec 3, 1971 (Box 24, Item 13685)
  - QuEST course # 128 Mr. Nancoo of Montreal, Canada, Jan 6, 1972 (Box 25, Item 13784)
  - MES State Conference, JHS All Day Conference, Jan 8, 1972 (Box 25, Item 13781)
  - NY School of Printing Guidance Counselors Self-Help Program, Jan 18, 1972 (Box 26, Item 13800)
  - Sight Clinic, Feb 29, 1972 (Box 27, Item 13877)
  - QuEST Course Secretaries, Feb 29, 1972 (Box 27, Item 13878)
  - Queens Mini QuEST Course, Apr 30, 1972 (Box 28, Item 13962)
  - PS 119 Brooklyn Drug prevention program, May 2, 1972 (Box 28, Item 13972)
  - Sickle Cell [Blood Testing for students], PS 167 Brooklyn, May 17, 1972 (Box 29, Item 14012)
- Series XVII: Publicity.
  - PS 199 New School Repro[duction] ["This will be your new neighborhood school" image designed for advertising reproduction], Apr 24, 1962 (Box 2, Item 6962)
  - Distributing Leaflets at Alexander's[,] Rego Park, Sep 7, 1965 (Box 4, Item 9153)
  - Press Conf[erence] Freedom Schools [Charles Cogen], Nov 10, 1965 (Box 4, Item 9391)
  - Press Conference CCED, Feb 2, 1966 (Box 4, Item 9638)
  - Career Exhibit [at] Kingsbridge Armory [UFT's "Teaching as a Career" booth pictured.], May 1, 1967 (Box 5, Item 10464)
  - Press Conference, Apr 29, 1968 (Box 6, Item 11164)
  - [David] Suskind lean [?] WNEW-TV channel 5 [TV taping], Jan 1, 1969 (Box 7, Item 11627)
  - Gracie Mansion [man in car being questioned by press], Oct 31, 1969 (Box 9, Item 12161)
  - TV Taping PS 130, Apr 7, 1970 (Box 11, Item 12487)
  - George Washington H. S. Press Conference, Apr 17, 1970 (Box 12, Item 12519)
  - Press Conference - Shanker Para-Professionals, Apr 20, 1970 (Box 12, Item 12523)
  - Press Conference, Jun 11, 1970 (Box 13, Item 12677)
  - Press Conference, Sep 9, 1970 (Box 14, Item 12742)
  - News Conference [Al] Shanker & Central Labor Council - endorsing Barry Farber Commodore, Oct 26, 1970 (Box 15, Item 12845)
  - School Board press conference PS 6, Oct 29, 1970 (Box 15, Item 12853)
  - Press Conference Budget, Jan 12, 1971 (Box 17, Item 13002)
  - Press Conference - Para-Professional College Apps., Feb 3, 1971 (Box 17, Item 13049)
  - Press Conference College Scholarship, Feb 18, 1971 (Box 17, Item 13085)
  - Press Conference City Coalition, Mar 4, 1971 (Box 18, Item 13119)
  - Julia Richmond HS Frontlash Press Conference, May 13, 1971 (Box 21, Item 13300)
  - Press Conference - Albert Shanker, Oct 12, 1971 (Box 23, Item 13521)
  - [Al] Shanker / Rockefeller Press Conference, Oct 29, 1971 (Box 23, Item 13581)
  - District 1 Press Conference Commodore, Dec 1, 1971 (Box 24, Item 13687)
  - Food & Maritime HS Manhattan, John Hall [Students cooking and adults (teachers?) taste-testing. There is a film crew visible in the shoot, filming the activities.], Dec 22, 1971 (Box 25, Item 13754)
  - Ad Hoc Comm. City University Press Conference, Jan 23, 1972 (Box 26, Item 13806)
  - PS 186 Manhattan Press Conference & School Damages, Feb 23, 1972 (Box 27, Item 13866)
  - UFCT & Legisl. Conf., Press Conference, Mar 29, 1972 (Box 28, Item 13925)
  - Press Conference Shanker - Roberts, May 30, 1972 (Box 29, Item 14034)
  - Press Conference [Beaure endorsement?], May 18, 1973 (Box 30, Item 14355)
- Series XVIII: Retired Teachers.
  - [Retirement Board], undated (Box 2, Item 7304)
  - Board of Education Teachers Retirement Board Election Winner, Oct 30, 1962 (Box 2, Item 7216)
  - Retired Teachers, May 14, 1968 (Box 6, Item 11216)
  - Retired Teachers Marc Ballroom, Oct 15, 1968 (Box 6, Item 11422)
  - Tax Committee of Retired Teachers Chapter [Grace Levinson, Edith Goldman (gets help), Mildred Haselkorn, Beulah Lipsky, Leah Isaacs], Mar 11, 1969 (Box 7, Item 11707)
  - Retired Teachers, May 13, 1969 (Box 8, Item 11879)
  - Retired Teachers - Congressman [ Leonard] Farbstein, Apr 24, 1970 (Box 12, Item 12537)
  - Board of Education Mitchell Rubin Swearing in Retirement Board, May 7, 1970 (Box 12, Item 12561)
  - Retirement Teachers Luncheon Grand St. Boys Club, May 12, 1970 (Box 12, Item 12581)
  - Committee Ret. Teachers, Oct 12, 1971 (Box 23, Item 13525)
  - Teachers Retirement Board Scott/Wittes, Nov 1, 1971 (Box 24, Item 13588)
  - Retired Teachers Committee Sylvia Levinson, Marc Ballroom, 16th st., Nov 9, 1971 (Box 24, Item 13613)
  - Marc Ballroom Retired Teachers Mr. Suval, Feb 8, 1972 (Box 26, Item 13827)
  - Retired teachers luncheon Albert Shanker Speaking St. Moritz [?] Hotel, May 9, 1972 (Box 28, Item 13976)
- Series XIX: School Districts.
  - District Negotiators Groups, Oct 17, 1967 (Box 6, Item 10839)
  - District 19 Brooklyn [children and adults demonstrating for restoration of funds cut from budget], May 7, 1968 (Box 6, Item 11190)
  - District 3 Manhattan Simon Schwartz 4 Group, Jan 14, 1969 (Box 6, Item 11591)
  - District 1 George Fesko, Jan 15, 1969 (Box 7, Item 11593)
  - District 12 No Quorum, Jan 17, 1969 (Box 7, Item 11603)
  - District 10 Sanford Blair (Herbert Renner), Jan 20, 1969 (Box 7, Item 11608)
  - District 29 Herb Magidson, Andrew Jackson HS, Susan Dorreck PS 156, Gloria Weinman PS 176 & Gladys Roth, Jan 21, 1969 (Box 7, Item 11607)
  - District 27 Tom Pappas, Jan 30, 1969 (Box 7, Item 11642)
  - District 22 Peter Goodman, Feb 4, 1969 (Box 7, Item 11643)
  - District 14 Marshall Levenfer, Feb 6, 1969 (Box 7, Item 11650)
  - District 6 Bruce Davidson, Feb 7, 1969 (Box 7, Item 11648)
  - District 10 Sanford Blair, Feb 17, 1969 (Box 7, Item 11664)
  - District 4 - Bill Kilgour (Kenneth Weissman incumbent), Feb 27, 1969 (Box 7, Item 11684)
  - District 16 Alan B. Lubin, (Eileen Lubin - Stephen Epstein), Feb 28, 1969 (Box 7, Item 11691)
  - Board of Education [Protest] 2 Bridges Picket, Mar 26, 1969 (Box 7, Item 11747)
  - 2 Bridges gov. [?] Board Election, Sep 18, 1969 (Box 8, Item 12055)
  - District 25 Rep. Election JHS 169 Queens, Sep 26, 1969 (Box 8, Item 12068)
  - Picket line Distr. Board of Ed [at] 1967 Turnbull Avenue [Bronx], Oct 20, 1969 (Box 9, Item 12130)
  - School Damage 2 Bridges District, Feb 20, 1970 (Box 10, Item 12403)
  - Seward Park H. S. Counsel Assembly District 5 [?] [or District 1], May 13, 1970 (Box 12, Item 12584)
  - District 28 Terrace-on-the-Park, May 22, 1970 (Box 12, Item 12611)
  - District PS 20 Demonstration, Jun 11, 1970 (Box 13, Item 12679)
  - District Supt. Office District 28, Jun 15, 1970 (Box 14, Item 12682)
  - District 19 Conference, Jul 9, 1970 (Box 14, Item 12717)
  - District 2 Reps, Dec 17, 1970 (Box 16, Item 12977)
  - District 15 Supervisors Penn Garden, Jan 9, 1971 (Box 16, Item 12996)
  - District 20 Brooklyn, Scholarship Party, Jan 14, 1971 (Box 17, Item 13013)
  - District 28 [Dr. Martin Luther] King Program, Jan 21, 1971 (Box 17, Item 13027)
  - District 2, 210 East 33rd st., Mar 5, 1971 (Box 18, Item 13125)
  - District 28 Queens overcrowded classes demonstration, May 6, 1971 (Box 20, Item 13268)
  - District 20 Funeral Procession to City Hall [Protest signs read "Budget Cuts Kill Public Schools"], May 7, 1971 (Box 20, Item 13273)
  - Leichter Party District 20 La Mere, May 18, 1971 (Box 21, Item 13312)
  - AAEU District 8 [basketball], May 21, 1971 (Box 21, Item 13330)
  - District 14 Summer Program Brooklyn, Jul 20, 1971 (Box 22, Item 13448)
  - District 9 [speakers], Sep 22, 1971 (Box 22, Item 13489)
  - District #5 Demonstration, Oct 14, 1971 (Box 23, Item 13529)
  - Security Conference District 17 Brooklyn, Oct 29, 1971 (Box 23, Item 13580)
  - District 1 Press Conference Commodore, Dec 1, 1971 (Box 24, Item 13687)
  - District 14 Human Relations course (Brooklyn), Jan 5, 1972 (Box 25, Item 13777)
  - La Paville District 20 Brooklyn, Jan 27, 1972 (Box 26, Item 13816)
  - Comm. [?] School Board District 6 Manhattan, Wadsworth, Feb 17, 1972 (Box 27, Item 13847)
  - Farmingdale School District [classroom], Mar 13, 1972 (Box 27, Item 13895)
  - District 2 Reception, Dr. Shapiro, Apr 14, 1972 (Box 28, Item 13937)
  - District 4 Candidates, Apr 7, 1973 (Box 30, Item 14297)
  - District 13 Brooklyn Fair, May 31, 1973 (Box 30, Item 14375)
  - End of Year Party District 15 Brooklyn, Jun 6, 1973 (Box 30, Item 14381)
  - District 6 School Board [Whitestone Photos], May 5, 1974 (Box 30, Item 14631)
  - District 6, Jose Spinoza [Whitestone Photos], May 6, 1974 (Box 30, Item 14634)
- Series XX: Schools/Students/Teachers.
  - IS 293 Brooklyn Puerto Rican Night, undated (Box 24, Item 13629)
  - C[ogen, Charles?] & K[olodny, Jules?] First Polio Shots NY School Children PS 61 ["Polio Pioneers 1954" logo on banner reading: "New York School Children Join National Field Trials of Salk Polio Vaccine"], Apr 27, 1954 (Box 1, Item 1792)
  - C[ogen, Charles?] & K[olodny, Jules?] Polio Vaccination PS 165 (Queens ) Flushing, May 4, 1954 (Box 1, Item 1811)
  - C[ogen, Charles?] & K[olodny, Jules?] Polio [Vaccination] P. S. 29 [Staten Island], Jun 11, 1954 (Box 1, Item 1895)
  - Teachers' [Guild?] [NY] Public Library Tess Cohen Grafford Book, Dec 13, 1955 (Box 1, Item 2732)
  - United Federation of Teachers Hughes High School, Oct 5, 1960 (Box 2, Item 5875)
  - Mabel Dean Bacon HS, Feb 3, 1961 (Box 2, Item 6150)
  - High School of Fashions, Feb 14, 1962 (Box 2, Item 6777)
  - PS 199 New School Repro[duction] ["This will be your new neighborhood school" image designed for advertising reproduction], Apr 24, 1962 (Box 2, Item 6962)
  - Rally HS of Fashion, Mar 20, 1963 (Box 3, Item 7539)